<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Geofrey Ernest Katesigwa on the web</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Geofrey Ernest Katesigwa on the web</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 09:37:36 +0300</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Week3 and 4</title>
      <link>/post/week_3_and_4/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 28 Sep 2019 09:37:36 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/week_3_and_4/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks have passed already. I used to believe I can handle having a day job and get time to explore my other open source interests, which has proved to be hard.
I&amp;rsquo;m glad I&amp;rsquo;m working fulltime on open source project though, so I have decided to fully shift my focus on the tyk gateway
This probably marks the end on updates on other projects I have been working on on my free time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 2</title>
      <link>/post/week-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Sep 2019 10:35:57 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/week-2/</guid>
      <description>This week has slowed down a little bit. It is more a research week,I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to do what I thought I would do, like working on hoodie because I just realized I might have even better ways to achieve my goals.
Work No PR was submitted to the tyk gateway this week, however I have been onto some cool stuff that might prove useful to the gateway someday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Week 1</title>
      <link>/post/week-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Sep 2019 10:10:22 +0300</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/week-1/</guid>
      <description>Week 1 updates This is my first of many updates that I plan to write on weekly basis. The updates will cover what I have accomplished in a week. The focus is mainly on work and my open source contributions. This will alaso include any lessons I pick up on weekly basis.
What weekly updates should be about  should be about open source and my work ( I am currently working fulltime on an open source project tyk) should be brief and concise (These are not blog posts, they are like a notebook to keep tabs of whet I have been up to) should be about programming should end with what I plan or wish to work on the following week  Work It has been three months since I started working on tyk, so this is a recap of the work I have done in the past three months.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>